hi thanks I'm glad everyone's chimed in
嗨，谢谢，我很高兴每个人都被编入
to see my presentation here about
在这里看到我的演讲
debugging and maintaining spring good
调试和维护spring好
application my name is Greg turn quest
应用我的名字叫格雷格转任务
you can follow me on Twitter a little
你可以在Twitter上关注我一点
bit of information of I happened to
我的一些信息碰巧
write a book on learning spring boot
写一本关于学习 spring boot 的书
that came out late last year so some of
去年下半年出来的，所以一些
those contents inspired by what I wrote
这些内容受我写的东西启发
in there and so I hope you can find some
在那儿，所以我希望你能找到一些
interest in there and if you'd like to
对那里感兴趣，如果您想
hear about updates about either the code
听到有关任一代码的更新
that behind that but the feeding in
在那后面，但在喂养
votes or other technical stuff you know
选票或其他您知道的技术资料
I'm sure to sign up
我一定要报名
we have a few links here the you may
我们在这里有一些链接，您可能
want to go check out if you want to keep
想去看看是否要保留
up with some of the spring stuff that's
一些春天的东西
coming out either videos or clear
出现视频或清晰
actions and stuff or other other forums
动作和东西或其他论坛
but what we're going to talk about today
但是我们今天要谈论的是
is debugging boot apps and then also
正在调试启动应用，然后
building you know some valuable support
建立您知道一些有价值的支持
tools that's for your ops team for your
适用于您的运营团队的工具
manager for your managers manager and
经理为您的经理经理和
other things like that and above all how
诸如此类的其他事情，最重要的是
fun it is to do it with delay spring
有趣的是延迟Spring 可以做到这一点
boot operates as we dive into this here
启动，因为我们在这里深入了解
I have about 19 slides here but most of
我这里有大约19张幻灯片，但大多数
this webinar is actually going to be
这次网络研讨会实际上是
live coding or you know running stuff to
实时编码，或者您知道要运行的东西
my IDE seeing how to use it but we're
我的IDE知道如何使用它，但是我们
going to kick things off and talk about
即将开始讨论
spring boot applications and you know if
spring boot 应用程序，你知道如果
you've been using the spring boot in the
您一直在使用 spring boot
past two years I'm sure you'll agree
过去两年我肯定你会同意
with me that the apps are really pretty
跟我说这些应用真的很漂亮
awesome there's some key aspects of
很棒，其中有一些关键方面
beautiful applications in scotch long
苏格兰威士忌的美丽应用
puts it that make it really powerful and
把它变得强大起来
on the bill they have auto configured
在他们已经自动配置的账单上
beans that based upon class path
基于类路径的bean
settings will switch on features it's
设置将打开它的功能
it's easy to take properties and
很容易取得财产和
externalize them and even put in profile
外化他们，甚至放在个人资料中
specific property so things like test
具体属性，例如测试
platforms or production or development
平台或生产或开发
platforms can in the bend your app is
平台可以弯腰您的应用程序是
needed
需要
things like runnable jar files are
像可运行的jar文件之类的东西是
another thing and then boots ability to
另一件事，然后启动能力
pre pick harmonized libraries so you
预选协调库，让您
know that stuff works together and a lot
知道东西可以一起工作
more stuff like that these are some of
像这样的更多东西是一些
the characteristics and boot that are a
特征和引导是
woolly candy in fact Josh long captured
羊毛糖实际上是乔什（Josh）早就被捕
it in a message that he posted at one
在他张贴在一条消息中
time that said working with spring boot
说用 spring boot 工作的时间
is like pair programming with the spring
就像与Spring 配对编程
developers so well I think we all agree
开发人员很好，我认为我们都同意
that spring boot is a really nice
spring boot 真的很好
platform to build applications upon but
在以下平台上构建应用程序的平台
one thing that we all need to
我们都需要做的一件事
acknowledge is the sooner or later we
承认是迟早我们
have trouble with apps they break in
他们闯入的应用程序有麻烦
some fashion or another and maybe when
一些时尚或其他，也许什么时候
you're trying to start things up and you
您正在尝试开始工作，而您
haven't maybe something's not too
也许还不太好
figured correctly or you run into an
想得对，否则您遇到了
issue
问题
you're trying to figure out what is it
你试图弄清楚是什么
is it the code that I wrote and it's
是我写的代码吗？
something that's misconfigured with boot
引导配置错误
and at this point things like Auto
在这一点上，像自动
configured beans suddenly become
配置的bean突然变成
frightening because we don't you know we
害怕，因为我们不知道
don't know what did spring do what what
不知道春天做了什么
did I do is it mean was it boot is there
我要做的是这意味着启动了吗
some setting I can do what what are my
在某些环境下我可以做什么
options here you know years ago when the
您几年前就知道这里的选项
spring framework introduced auto wiring
Spring 框架介绍自动接线
you know a lot of people were afraid of
你知道很多人都害怕
it because it seemed a little magical
它，因为它似乎有点神奇
but over time people came to adopt it
但是随着时间的流逝，人们开始采用它
wasn't interested how it operated and
对它的运作方式不感兴趣，
the error messages and the things that
错误信息以及
came from that made it a very usable
来自它使它非常有用
technology and you know I for example
技术，例如，你知道我
use auto wiring all the time and in a
始终使用自动接线
similar fashion spring boot has some
类似的时尚 spring boot 有一些
stuff to help you in this arena when we
当我们在这个领域帮助您的东西
talk about Auto configured beans so you
谈论自动配置的bean，这样您
know if you run into an issue it would
知道你是否遇到了问题
really be nice to look up what spring
真的很高兴仰望什么春天
dude did in the situation and for this
花花公子做了这种情况，为此
we have a couple demo apps we're going
我们有几个演示应用程序，我们要
to start with one and they both kind of
从一个开始，他们俩都
do the same thing but they're going to
做同样的事情，但他们将
let us look at different bits of what
让我们看一下不同的地方
boot gives us to help us solve this
引导给我们帮助我们解决这个问题
problem so before we get into demo mode
问题，所以在进入演示模式之前
I want to describe what the what this
我想描述一下这是什么
little toy application does it's a
小玩具应用程序是
really tiny application and what it
很小的应用程序及其
simulates is devices out in the field
模拟现场设备
reporting alarm status and piping from
从以下位置报告警报状态和管道
on the left-hand side routing them
在左侧路由它们
through an active entity message broker
通过活动实体消息代理
into our event processing center on the
进入我们的活动处理中心
right in this case we just I've I picked
在这种情况下，我们只是选择了
out three host names here they were
列出了三个主机名
going to generate messages and post them
将生成消息并将其发布
and then on the right hand side will be
然后在右侧
a consumer receiving them on the other
消费者在另一方接收它们
end
结束
so let's get into demo mode and look at
让我们进入演示模式，看看
some code so I'm gonna pull it out of
一些代码，所以我要把它拉出来
keynote here and I'm going to switch
这里的主题演讲，我要切换
over to my IDE and then I'm gonna put
转到我的IDE，然后我要放
this thing into presentation mode so you
这个东西进入演示模式，所以你
can actually see it
可以看到
okay so I have a few to do's here that I
好，所以我要在这里做些事
want to I want to cover some stuff here
我想在这里覆盖一些东西
this is my build files I happen to be
这是我的生成文件，我碰巧是
using Gradle and in this case we're
使用Gradle，在这种情况下，我们
using spring boot one two three one two
使用 spring boot 一二三一二
three now at the Melissa list of
现在在Melissa列表中有3个
dependencies up at the top this isn't
依赖关系在顶部不是
stuff I need for my application to
我需要申请的东西
function I have a spring boot starter
功能我有一个Spring 启动启动器
this brings a core feature set actually
这实际上带来了核心功能
use spring JMS because we're going to be
使用spring JMS，因为我们将
doing the both posting and consuming
同时进行发布和消费
messages over Jayma we're going to use
通过Jayma发送的消息，我们将使用
things like the JMS conflate to do that
像JMS这样的东西可以做到这一点
and on top of that we're using ActiveMQ
最重要的是，我们正在使用ActiveMQ
now you notice in all three you know
现在您注意到所有三个
this was a good the good old I don't
这是一个好东西，我不喜欢
have to supply the version numbers
必须提供版本号
because the spring boot Gradle plug-in
因为Spring Boot Gradle插件
is doing that for me it's nice to know
正在为我做这件事，很高兴知道
is in this version of the supported
在受支持的此版本中
version of ActiveMQ it actually comes
它实际上是ActiveMQ版本
with an embedded broker model so I don't
使用嵌入式经纪人模型，所以我不
even have to stand up a separate
甚至不得不单独站起来
ActiveMQ instance I can run it right out
我可以立即运行ActiveMQ实例
of the box here but down here there's a
在这里的盒子，但在这里下面有一个
couple extra bits that I've added on now
我现在添加的几个额外的位
this is not part of my functional
这不是我功能的一部分
application this is what sometimes
应用程序有时
referred to as non-functional stuff and
称为非功能性材料和
one that's the spring boot actuator what
一个是Spring 启动器
it does is it serves me up what's called
它确实是为我服务的
an auto configuration report which will
自动配置报告
tell me every rule that boot kicked in
告诉我启动的所有规则
when it came to configuring beans for me
在为我配置bean时
and then the other piece is is to
然后另一件是
actually serve it up on a web page we
实际上将其投放在我们的网页上
need the spring MVC web starter here hmm
这里需要Spring MVC Web Starter
I'll need to make sure that I have
我需要确保我有
comment this out because we're not ready
注释掉这个，因为我们还没准备好
for that yet
为此
so I'm going to here is let's just let's
所以我要去这里，让我们
launch this application and take a look
启动这个应用程序，看看
and see what happens you what we're
看看你怎么了，我们是什么
doing
在做
you
您
okay it gets underway here what I'm
好吧，我现在在这里进行
going to do is I'm going to pause the
我要做的是暂停
output
输出
look at what's happening and then we're
看看发生了什么，然后我们
going to open up a little bit of code
要打开一点代码
just to see what it what it's up to to
只是看看它在做什么
understand what's happening you know
了解发生了什么，你知道
we're running this app on Tomcat for
我们正在Tomcat上运行此应用程序
8080 like any standard web application
8080像任何标准的Web应用程序一样
down here I can see that there's a you
在这里，我可以看到有一个你
know this little indicator here tells me
知道这里的这个小指标告诉我
that we're on the VM localhost meaning
我们在VM本地主机上
this is the sign of an embedded apache
这是嵌入式apache的标志
activemq broker and down here at the
activemq经纪人，在这里
bottom are starting to see this traffic
底部开始看到此流量
come out and to see where that's coming
出来看看那是哪里
from I'm going to pull up the code now
现在我要提取代码
in the earlier diagram we saw on the
在前面的图中，我们在
left hand side that there were there
左边那边有
were three host names router you know
你知道的三个主机名路由器
these and you can see in here router 101
这些，您可以在这里看到路由器101
multiplex 205 and switch 1143
复用器205和开关1143
essentially this little simulator is
本质上，这个小模拟器是
pretending to generate traffic for me
假装为我带来流量
what it's doing it says it's scheduled
它说的是计划的
to run their simulation every 1000
每1000个运行一次模拟
milliseconds so what it does is it
毫秒，它是做什么的
randomly picks one of these host names
随机选择这些主机名之一
down here it will then randomly pick the
在这里，它将随机选择
severity of the alarm whether it's
警报的严重性
up-down degraded or jeopardy and
上下降级或危及
basically puts you know assembles an
基本上让您知道组装
alarm event and then what it does is
警报事件，然后它要做的是
here we have a JMS complete so it'll
在这里，我们有一个完整的JMS，所以它将
just ship it out over it's over a
只是把它运过来
message queue so that's the left-hand
消息队列，所以这是左手
side of that architectural diagram
该架构图的一面
generating traffic from the from the
从产生流量
field now on the other side of that I
现在在另一边我
have a consumer first of all you know
首先要有一个消费者
the consumer is set up annotated as a
消费者被设置为
spring component meaning you know it
Spring 组件意味着您知道
will automatically be picked up and
将被自动提取并
activated and then down here I'm using
激活，然后在这里我正在使用
spring I believe latest 4.1 but it could
春天，我相信最新的4.1，但它可以
be 4.2 new at JMS listener so this is
是JMS侦听器上的4.2新版，所以这是
all I need to say whenever a message
每当有消息我只需要说
comes in on this channel run event you
出现在这个频道运行事件中
know be serialized the payload into an
知道将有效载荷序列化为
alarm event and
警报事件和
into those methods now in this case I'm
现在在这种情况下进入这些方法
just logging the message out to disk and
只是将消息注销到磁盘，然后
after the console which we can see down
在我们可以看到的控制台之后
on the slogs
在口号上
but you know this is where in reality
但是你知道这是现实
you could have a fancy event correlation
你可能有一个花哨的事件关联
algorithm that could pipe traffic to the
可以将流量传输到
customer can correlate alarms with
客户可以将警报与
customer resources and you know open
客户资源，您知道开放
tickets that kind of sealed process and
那种密封的票证和
stuff right now we're just printing it
现在，我们只是在打印它
out
出
so as it goes here you know it keeps and
所以当它走到这里时，你知道它一直在
keeps generating traffic in the
持续在
background and so that's that's good
背景，那就是很好
you
您
I'm going to be switch out of
我将要退出
presentation mode and go over to my
演示模式并转到我的
browser
浏览器
you
您
I want to show you a this is the I
我想给你看一个，这就是我
mentioned earlier an auto configuration
前面提到的自动配置
report one of them is going to collapse
报告其中之一将要崩溃
us down here but this is this is an end
我们在这里，但这就是结束
web endpoint that's served up by spring
Spring提供的Web端点
boot actuators what it does is it
引导执行器的作用是什么
collects every rule that gets processed
收集所有要处理的规则
to restring boot these are these
重新启动这些是这些
conditional bean definitions of a lot of
很多的条件bean定义
them driven by what's on your class path
他们是由你上课的路上所驱动
and here it splits them into two camps
在这里将它们分成两个阵营
the first one are rules that turned out
第一个是原来的规则
true you know a rule that spots things
是的，您知道规则可以发现事物
like spring MVC on the class pass so it
像春季MVC在课堂上通过，所以
turns on some spring MVC configuration
打开一些Spring MVC配置
these are under the positive match ones
这些在正匹配项下
and then rules that don't get matched or
然后没有匹配的规则
in other words that don't kick in and
换句话说，不会踢和
generate beans go into the negative
产生 Bean type 进入负面
matches now the report is actually very
现在匹配，该报告实际上非常
compact JSON document but I haven't had
紧凑的JSON文档，但我还没有
the JSON view plug-in in my browser to
浏览器中的JSON视图插件
make it readable so if I shrink it all
使它可读，所以如果我全部缩小
down but only open up the positive I can
向下但只开放正面
look for things like ActiveMQ you know
寻找类似ActiveMQ的东西
me hover over here to highlight here's
我将鼠标悬停在此处以突出显示
one of the here's one of the rule sets
这是规则集之一
ActiveMQ auto-configuration and when i
ActiveMQ自动配置以及何时
look at this i can see that it had two
看着这个，我可以看到它有两个
conditions could satisfy for this rule
条件可以满足此规则
to kick down one was it was dependent on
踢一个是依赖
finding a class in the class path in
在课程路径中查找课程
this case looking for the JMS connection
这种情况下寻找JMS连接
factory interface and also for the
工厂界面，也用于
active mq connection factory
活跃的MQ连接工厂
implementation class so this only works
实现类，所以这仅适用
essentially if you have active and queue
本质上，如果您有活动和排队
on your class path it also has a
在您的上课路上，它也有一个
condition that there is it says
有说的条件
conditional on missing bean connection
以缺少bean连接为条件
factory that means that this rule only
工厂，这意味着仅此规则
kicks in if you did not define your own
如果您未定义自己的项目，则会加入
connection factory so in other words if
连接工厂，换句话说，如果
you don't define one spring boot will
你没有定义一个 spring boot
define a connection factory can link up
定义工厂可以链接的连接
to active mq however if you want to go
活跃的MQ但是，如果你想去
make your define your own connection
让您定义自己的连接
factory that's fine you can declare it
可以的工厂可以声明它
and let spring boot will do is
让Spring Boot做的是
essentially back off and not
本质上退缩而不是
take this soon and so will let you take
尽快接受，这样您就可以接受
control of the situation and in my
控制局势，在我
opinion the backing off aspect of spring
认为春天的退缩
boon is something that is going to start
恩赐即将开始
to appear and lakhs of next generation
出现和下一代
frameworks latest force frameworks to
框架最新的力量框架
scale and respond to developer intent
扩展并响应开发人员的意图
you know down here there's another of
你知道在这里还有另外一个
activemq based one called activemq
基于activemq的一种叫做activemq
connection factory configuration and
连接工厂配置和
this this is some more stuff to do a
这是要做的更多事情
connection factory I gotta go into that
我要去的连接工厂
now right above here there actually
现在就在这里上面
happens to be some more stuff here these
这些恰好是更多的东西
all when we find a spot to a pause out
当我们找到一个停顿点的时候
here so the screen can catch up there
在这里，屏幕可以在那里赶上
settle here that are also tied with JMS
在这里定居，也与JMS有联系
you know active in queues not the only
你知道活跃在队列中不是唯一的
JMS broker so we have one set of Auto
JMS经纪人，所以我们有一套自动
configurations based on acted and queue
基于代理和队列的配置
but another that's totally dedicated to
但是另一个完全致力于
spring JMS settings you know this one
Spring JMS设置，您知道这一点
down here
在这里
JMS auto-configuration pound JMS
JMS自动配置磅
template but this says is if there is no
模板，但这是如果没有
being of type JMS template spring google
类型为JMS模板的Google春季版
create one for you now up above is a
现在为您创建一个以上
enclosing class that says well this only
封闭类，只说得好
applies if we can detect JMS template on
如果我们可以在以下位置检测到JMS模板，则适用
the class path so it sees JMS template
类路径，以便它可以看到JMS模板
on the class path and if it sees a
在类路径上，如果看到
connection factory beam definition and
连接工厂梁定义和
down here it will generate a JMS
在这里它将生成一个JMS
template unless you define your own JMS
模板，除非您定义自己的JMS
template
模板
that's a little bit about how to decode
关于如何解码的一点点
what this auto-configuration report is
此自动配置报告是什么
showing let me go back to presentation
显示让我回到演示文稿
mode of the IDE and let me go pull up
IDE的模式，让我继续上拉
that Jamis auto-configuration class that
Jamis自动配置类
we were just talking about so here we
我们只是在谈论所以在这里我们
can actually read the same thing these
可以真正读到这些相同的东西
are the here we go
我们去的地方
so this says this configuration and
所以这说这个配置和
doesn't kick in unless they can see JMS
除非他们能看到JMS，否则不会介入
translate on the class path and that
在类路径上翻译
there is a beam type connection Factory
有一个梁式连接工厂
down here is that little is that beam
在这下面是那束光
down here that says that there's no JMS
在这里说没有JMS
you know this beam is missing the Janus
你知道这束光缺少Janus
template Ike beam it will define one for
模板Ike梁，它将定义一个
us so you know this gives us we have
我们，所以你知道这给了我们
essentially what it's telling us is we
从本质上讲，这是在告诉我们
have options here we can plug in our own
这里有选项，我们可以插入自己的
connection factor if we want we will
连接因子，如果我们想要的话
back off that part we can plug in our
退出那一部分，我们可以插入我们的
own JMS template if we want Google back
自己的JMS模板（如果我们希望Google返回）
off on that part so that's one degree of
在那部分上，这是一个程度
granularity to go in and do stuff but
进去做事情的粒度，但是
another option is that the spring boot
另一个选择是 spring boot
has this amazing property support so
有这个惊人的财产支持，所以
sometimes you don't want to override an
有时您不想覆盖
entire beam definition just to change
整个光束的定义只是为了改变
one parameter inside it
其中一个参数
now what I'm going to do is exit
现在我要做的是退出
presentation modes so far we've been
到目前为止的演示模式
running this app with the embedded
嵌入式运行此应用程序
broker oh okay I already stopped it okay
经纪人哦，好的，我已经停止了
yes I did
是的，我做到了
all right no way time this is the wrong
没事没办法，这是错误的
get to the other one okay
到另一个
I'm gonna stop this instance here
我要在这里停止这个实例
so let me wait I'm sorry Mia relaunch it
所以让我等待，对不起Mia重新启动它
exits full screen mode and then let's go
退出全屏模式，然后开始
look at property settings so we just
看一下属性设置，所以我们只是
looked at an auto configuration report
看了一个自动配置报告
we saw some stuff that had kicked in we
我们看到了一些踢进我们的东西
went and were able to actually look up
去了，能够真正地抬头
what the code was thanks to the power of
凭借强大的功能，代码是什么
open source now we can actually look at
开源，现在我们可以实际看一下
another end point config props if I
另一个端点配置道具，如果我
search for activemq I'm going to find
搜索我将要找到的activemq
this one down here this just property
这一个在这里这只是财产
settings we have the ability to override
设置，我们有能力覆盖
you'll notice the prefix is spring
您会注意到前缀是spring
ActiveMQ and then underneath is a list
ActiveMQ，然后在下面是一个列表
of independent property so we can use
具有独立财产，因此我们可以使用
spring ActiveMQ and if you look at the
春天的ActiveMQ，如果您看一下
last property says in memory true but
内存中的最后一个属性表示正确，但
that is telling us is we have options we
告诉我们我们有选择权
can override the in-memory one and say
可以覆盖内存中的一个并说
no I don't want to use in-memory I want
不，我不想使用我想要的内存
to understand a lot of broker let me
了解很多经纪人让我
switch that it's an opportunity to
切换这是一个机会
switch it defaults if we're running a
如果我们正在运行
standalone broker and it's on a
独立经纪人，它在
different URL maybe a non-standard one
不同的URL可能是非标准的URL
we can go plug that in we can plug in
我们可以插入，我们可以插入
other settings to override it so in this
其他设置以覆盖它，所以在此
case I'm gonna stop the app we go to my
万一我要停止应用程序，我们去我的
we go back to presentation mode for this
为此，我们回到演示模式
keep it readable
保持可读性
open it up here so here all I need to do
在这里打开它，这就是我要做的
is change this one property to false and
将这个属性更改为false，
this a year you need to do is checked if
这一年你需要做的检查
I'm running ActiveMQ
我正在运行ActiveMQ
okay stano's making sure it's down psych
好的，斯塔诺确保它的情绪低落
and then start it up again so here's
然后重新启动它，所以这里是
where I'm going to run separate active
我要在其中运行单独的活动
NQ standalone server so now if I start
NQ独立服务器，所以现在如果我启动
this thing up it's going just like it
这个东西就这样
was doing that before so this will start
之前已经做了，所以这将开始
up stuff
东西
and clicking a long thing you're okay so
然后点击一长条就可以了
we see some action let's go let's go
我们看到一些动作，我们走吧，我们走吧
back and look at that property setting
返回并查看该属性设置
that we just saw now we can see in
我们刚才看到的，我们可以看到
memory Falls and so what this is telling
记忆力下降，这说明了什么
us is that it's no longer using the in
我们是它不再使用
memory settings if I look back at that
记忆设置，如果我回头看
console in presentation mode here
在此处以演示模式控制台
if I pause the let me pause this output
如果我暂停让我暂停此输出
and back up to the beginning where it
并回到起点
launched you know we can see the same
发射你知道我们可以看到相同的
thing that it's Tomcat running on port
Tomcat在端口上运行的问题
8080 but if I look in the same area down
8080但如果我朝下看同一区域
here that I saw before I'm no longer see
在我消失之前看到的这里
that connected to VM localhost which was
连接到VM ​​localhost的
the indicator for a in-memory embedded
嵌入式内存指示器
activemq Broker so instead we can tell
activemq经纪人，所以相反，我们可以告诉
that it's talking to our external broker
它正在与我们的外部经纪人交谈
and that way with a single property
而且只有一个属性
setting change we were able to go in and
设定变更，我们得以进入
tweak the settings there and let's even
调整那里的设置，甚至
it's even more valuable as we also got
它甚至更有价值，因为我们也得到了
insight into other property settings
了解其他属性设置
till we get it okay let me get out of
直到我们知道了，让我离开
this and go back and look here and point
这个然后回去看看这里并指出
out you know there's other property we
你知道我们还有其他财产
can change the broker URL the password
可以更改经纪人URL的密码
we can configure it for if we need a
我们可以配置它，如果我们需要一个
pooled set of connections which isn't
集合的连接不是
often recommended case in production you
在生产中经常推荐的案例
know define user parameters if they're
知道是否定义用户参数
security on the broker all these can be
经纪人的安全所有这些都可以
configured through injectable properties
通过可注射属性配置
now one question that may arise is
现在可能出现的一个问题是
what's the benefit of this can I just go
我可以去这有什么好处
to the reference documents that are for
有关的参考文件
spring boot here and you know do some
spring boot 在这里，你知道做一些
searching to find out like okay well
寻找找出像好吧
here's why here's this tells me
这就是为什么这告诉我
everything I need to know right here why
我在这里需要知道的一切，为什么
do I need to go through all that or if I
我需要经历所有这些吗？
search you know further down on the
搜索您进一步了解的
documents I can find these other
我可以找到其他文件
property settings right here well the
属性设置就在这里
risk and that is that you know the
风险，那就是你知道
documents are good but sometimes
文件很好，但有时
documents and the version of the foe
文件和敌人的版本
you're using may not be in sync with
您正在使用的可能与
each other one may be out of date you
彼此可能已经过时了
may be looking at the wrong document and
可能看错了文件，并且
one thing that the documents can never
文件永远不能做的一件事
accommodate is people are starting to
适应是人们开始
write third-party libraries with
用编写第三方库
springle Auto configuration built in so
内置的springle自动配置
somebody else's property settings aren't
别人的属性设置不是
gonna peer these documents but I can
会浏览这些文件，但我可以
guarantee you any auto configured rule
向您保证任何自动配置的规则
will show up and that all the config
将会显示出来，并且所有的配置
report and any property whether it's
报告和任何财产，无论是
from spring boot or somebody else's
从 spring boot 或其他人的
module will definitely show up in here
模块肯定会显示在这里
I feel like this would you know
我想你会知道吗
encourages people to actually use a
鼓励人们实际使用
similar approach of taking key settings
进行关键设置的类似方法
and externalizing them through property
并通过财产外部化
settings
设定
so we can make it easier to manage
这样我们就可以更轻松地进行管理
applications
应用领域
okay now one other another bit of code
好吧，现在又是另一段代码
that I want to look at here um so far
我想到目前为止在这里看
we've talked about Auto configuration a
我们已经讨论过自动配置
report and then we've also talked about
报告，然后我们也谈到了
configuration settings there's another
配置设置还有另一个
bit of you know non-functional features
你们当中有些人知道非功能性功能
that come with food and that is health
食物带来健康
checks now spring boon comes with a
检查现在春天的恩赐带有
built in basically up/down check
内置基本上向上/向下检查
essentially when the app is running you
基本上是在应用运行时
can pull slash health and you'll get an
可以大大提高健康水平，
up message you can actually write custom
消息，您实际上可以编写自定义
health checks to go interrogate key
健康检查去询问钥匙
parts of your system and return the
系统的各个部分，然后返回
results back to spring boot actuator and
结果返回到Spring Boot Actuator
it will appear at the same place in this
它会出现在这个地方
case I wanted to write a check to make
我想写一张支票做的情况
sure that the ActiveMQ broker is up and
确保ActiveMQ代理已启动并且
running so to do that I need to declare
运行这样做，我需要声明
being the this case I'm going to have it
在这种情况下，我要拥有它
picked up by auto wiring with the spring
通过Spring 自动接线拾取
component Bank annotation that sentiment
成分银行注释情绪
spring booth actuators health indicator
Spring 箱执行器健康指示器
interface for it to be recognized now to
现在可以识别它的界面
do my check I need a handle on the JMS
做我的检查，我需要在JMS上进行处理
connection factory so here I'm using the
连接工厂，所以我在这里使用
a the well tested constructor injection
经过良好测试的构造函数注入
with auto wiring so this way when the
自动接线，这样当
component gets created automatically by
组件由自动创建
the springs dependency injection
Spring 依赖注入
container it will give me a copy of the
容器，它将给我一份副本
connection factory then when I actually
然后当我实际连接工厂
come along and do the health check it's
来做健康检查
going to basically try to do this call
基本上会尝试执行此呼叫
factory create connection so if it's not
工厂创建连接，所以如果不是
able to make a connection they'll throw
能够建立联系，他们会抛出
a JMS exception and in this case I can
JMS异常，在这种情况下，我可以
return a status down with a copy of the
返回状态并附带一份
exception however if this check works
但是，如果此检查有效
just fine and I can return an
很好，我可以退还
alternative message in this case I can
在这种情况下，我可以选择替代消息
return a status up message and I can
返回状态更新消息，我可以
throw in detail in this case you can
在这种情况下可以详细介绍
return the status up and you can add as
返回状态，您可以添加为
many attributes as you want to describe
您想要描述的许多属性
your city
您的城市
for this one I just have a single text
对于这个，我只有一个文本
message and so the broker was
消息，所以经纪人是
successfully reached sometimes in these
有时成功地达到了这些
kind of status messages people that were
状态消息的人
critical details like IP addresses or
IP地址或
they may the Kate usernames like the
他们可能会像Kate这样的用户名
what user is the system running under
系统在哪个用户下运行
some of this data is to be deemed as
其中一些数据应被视为
security sensitive data so actually by
安全敏感数据，实际上
default when you go look up the health
你去的时候默认查一下健康
status all you get is the up or down
您所获得的状态是向上还是向下
message to tell you whether or not a
消息告诉您是否
system is up it aggregates all the
系统启动时，它将所有
messages and so if everything is up it
消息，如果一切正常
gives you a blanket up statement but for
给你一揽子声明，但对于
this demo I wanted to actually show all
这个演示我想实际显示所有
the all the bits of health status at
健康状况的所有方面
once so I went in and told it to say now
一次所以我进去告诉它现在说
health data is not sensitive set it
健康数据不敏感设置它
defaults and show me everything so let's
默认值并向我显示所有内容，所以让我们
go look at that indicator first in the
首先在
browser and then we're going to go look
浏览器，然后我们去看看
at some of the stuff through another
在一些东西之间
interface
接口
so if I go to this health endpoint this
所以如果我去这个健康终点
is the this is the aggregate message up
这是汇总消息吗
here status up and if that other flag
在这里状态，如果那个其他标志
was not there that's all that I would
不在那里，我只想
get would be status up unless the user
除非用户没有，否则获取状态将为up
authenticates with a management approved
经批准的管理层进行身份验证
user ID and password and you're able to
用户ID和密码，您就可以
get the details
获取详细信息
it appears boot has a another default
看来启动还有另一个默认设置
health status indicator down here called
健康状况指示器在这里称为
disk space and then we see the one that
磁盘空间，然后我们看到
we just looked at a moment ago
我们刚才看了一下
here we see status up broker
在这里，我们可以看到经纪人的身份
successfully reached so in this sense
在这种意义上成功达成目标
you know it took me not ten lines of
你知道我花了不到十行
code perhaps to write a health check so
代码也许写健康检​​查，所以
you know when we go into the land of
你知道我们什么时候进入
micro services and things like that and
微服务之类的东西，以及
you need to start checking a lot of
您需要开始检查很多
different bits and pieces to make sure
不同的点点滴滴，以确保
everything is up this becomes a very
一切都好起来，这变得非常
easy tool to do that with
简单的工具可以做到这一点
now talking about status checks so far
现在为止谈论状态检查
we've been doing web checks you know
我们一直在做网络检查
this is for instance this end points
例如，这是终点
really handy when your system
当您的系统真的很方便
administrator or your ops team comes to
管理员或您的运营团队来
you and says I need to ping your app and
您，并说我需要ping您的应用程序，
tell if it's up you know I need to put a
告诉是否到了，你知道我需要放一个
green box up on this panel and then ek
在此面板上的绿色框，然后按ek
whether your app is running and you say
您的应用程序是否正在运行，您说
all right curl / health on my app and
我的应用程序上的所有卷曲/健康状况
that will tell you the story so they can
它将告诉您故事，以便他们可以
do that but sometimes people use other
这样做，但有时人们使用其他
other mechanisms
其他机制
one example is JMX JMX has been around
一个例子是JMX JMX已经存在
for a long time
需很长时间
I don't see it heavily used but there
我没有看到它被大量使用，但是在那里
are some shops that do that
有些商店这样做
so spring boot actuator actually comes
所以Spring Boot Actuator实际上来了
pre-built with support to talk to it let
预先建立并与之交谈的支持让
me make sure I'm talking to the right
我确保我说的正确
incidence yes so what I've launched here
是的，所以我在这里启动了
is J console J console comes out of the
是J控制台J控制台是从
box with any job installation now what
现在有任何作业安装的包装盒
they I'm going to point out is J console
我要指出的是J控制台
I don't have presentation mode for it so
我没有演示模式，所以
you can go ahead and use your want to
您可以继续使用自己的意愿
back zoom option at your end if you want
如果需要，可以在您的末端使用后缩放选项
to try to zoom in and see what I'm doing
尝试放大并查看我在做什么
I'm not I'm not going to do a lot of
我不是，我不会做很多事情
stuff here I'm just going to point out
我这里要指出的是
that it's available if I go into spring
如果我进入春天就可以使用
boot endpoints like here I can see this
像这里的启动端点，我可以看到这个
health endpoint because you know there's
健康终点，因为您知道
health endpoint I look at the operations
健康终点我看一下操作
there's a get Data button over here and
这里有一个“获取数据”按钮，
I hit that I'm gonna widen this out here
我想我要在这里扩大范围
I can kind of see the same data that I
我可以看到与我相同的数据
was seen on the web page you put the
您在网页上看到的
blood page in the background put these
在后台放血页
two side-by-side so I can see the
两个并排，所以我可以看到
is up I can see this ActiveMQ message
启动，我可以看到此ActiveMQ消息
and I can see bisque space it's uh not
我可以看到浓汤空间，这不是
necessarily in the same format but you
必须采用相同的格式，但您
know you can use somebody can use take
知道你可以使用某人可以使用
console to take a peek or because it's
控制台来偷看还是因为
over a standardized API of JMX api you
通过JMX api的标准化API
can write a Java app to connect directly
可以编写Java应用程序直接连接
to actuators jmx endpoint and you can
到执行器jmx端点，您可以
consume this data and do whatever you
消耗这些数据并做任何你想做的
want to with it let me close that and
想要它，让我结束
point out that all the endpoints that we
指出我们所有的端点
were looking at are also available here
也在看这里
we looked at the auto configuration
我们看了自动配置
report and I can do the same data
报告，我可以做同样的数据
operation and find it here I mentioned
操作，并在这里找到我提到的
about a compact report and this is it
关于一份紧凑的报告，就是这样
it's stuffed into the positive matches
它塞入正面比赛
and negative matches and so you have to
和否定匹配，因此您必须
go go in and digest all this stuff here
去这里消化所有这些东西
but all the materials there you know
但是那里的所有材料
we're looking at the configuration
我们在看配置
properties report the name of that end
属性报告该端的名称
point so we can still see all the stuff
这样我们仍然可以看到所有内容
here it's just it's just in another
在这里只是在另一个
format it's another option for you to
格式化这是您的另一种选择
pick from
从中选择
now what I'm going to do is going to
现在我要做的是
flip back to the slides here play
跳回到此处播放的幻灯片
so the quick recap we looked at we're
所以我们快速回顾一下
looking at spring mood actuator and what
看着春天的情绪促动器和什么
it gives us out of the box it gives us
它使我们开箱即用
an auto configuration report that tells
自动配置报告会告诉
us what rules matched what rules did not
我们哪些规则与哪些规则不匹配
match we have a health check which gives
匹配，我们有健康检查
us an opportunity to plug in our own
我们有机会插入自己的
checks you know I think boot has several
检查您知道我认为启动有几个
like it'll ping databases and things
像它会ping数据库和东西
like that but you know we wrote an
这样，但你知道我们写了
activemq broker check look at property
activemq经纪人检查一下物业
settings we also have an opportunity to
设置，我们也有机会
put custom application information at
将自定义应用程序信息放在
slash info I didn't pull that out but
斜线信息我没有拉出来，但
we'll we'll do that in a moment
我们一会儿再做
you can click text information like you
您可以点击您喜欢的文字信息
know the URL you know support website
知道您知道的URL支持网站
it's also possible in the you can look
你也可以看一下
it up in the reference documents to
在参考文件中
generate property data that has your get
生成可以获取的属性数据
like a get commit ID the the version
像获取提交ID的版本
that the app was going with so people
该应用程序与人们一起使用
can look up hey my hat broke this is a
可以抬起头，我的帽子坏了，这是一个
version I'm running
我正在运行的版本
you know if I go to this info endpoint
你知道我是否去这个信息终点
like it says you know here's details
喜欢它说你知道这里的细节
about my app you know one Golden Nugget
关于我的应用程序，您知道一个金块
tag here would be a you know a commit
标签在这里是一个你知道的提交
version number what version of the app
版本号应用程序的版本
are you running so that I don't have to
你在跑步，所以我不必
waste three hours figuring out that
浪费了三个小时才弄清楚
you're running a two-week old version
您正在运行两个星期的旧版本
and the issue you're seeing learning
和你看到的问题
patched now we talked about things like
现在打补丁，我们谈论诸如
debugging stuff and you know doing being
调试的东西，你知道做
able to figure out what happened with
能够弄清楚发生了什么事
auto-configuration reports being able to
自动配置报告能够
look at property settings so we can
查看属性设置，以便我们可以
override and writing some health checks
覆盖并编写一些健康检查
and what we're starting to cut over to
而我们开始切入
are the features that we need to support
是我们需要支持的功能
the ops team and spring boot comes with
运营团队和 spring boot 自带
a lot of support for that some key
对某些关键的很多支持
pieces of that include metrics we want
其中包括我们想要的指标
to collect data on what's happening in
收集有关发生的情况的数据
different fashions for that we're going
我们要去的不同时尚
to switch to a slightly altered version
切换到稍有改动的版本
of the demo the same problems face but
演示的相同问题，但
I'm going to stop this instance running
我将停止此实例的运行
okay shut that down
好吧，把它关掉
that is out and I'm going to close that
出来了，我要结束那个
once I don't into the end by accident
一旦我不偶然地走到尽头
let me puts back into presentation mode
让我回到演示模式
and only show what I what I mean let's
只显示我的意思让我们
see her
看她
okay essentially looking at the same
好吧，基本上看一样
consumer the same code that was on the
消费者使用相同的代码
right side of that architectural diagram
该架构图的右侧
that's consuming messages that team
这消耗了团队的信息
through DMS however what we're
通过DMS，但是我们
introducing here through constructor
通过构造函数在这里介绍
injection is spring boot actuators
注射是Spring Boot Actuator
counter service there's a repository of
柜台服务有一个仓库
metrics that collect things like
收集诸如
counters gauges other things counters
柜台计价器
are you you increment counters they can
你在增加计数器吗
go up by one that may be an option
可能是一个选择
incremented by more than that but you
增加了更多，但你
can increase and decrease counters
可以增加和减少计数器
essentially since this is an auto wired
基本上是因为这是自动连线
component I'm gonna you know I don't
我要你知道我不知道
have to actually create this being
必须实际创建这个存在
spring boot actuator goes ahead and
Spring Boot Actuator继续前进，
creates it for me so it down here this
为我创建它，所以在这里
is the same code earlier of consuming
与之前使用的代码相同
you know processing processing event but
你知道处理事件，但是
now I'm going to add a couple steps here
现在我要在这里添加几个步骤
and say increment this metric and here
并说增加这个指标
I'm on the fly defining a metric called
我正在定义一个指标
messages total dot consume so every
消息总点消耗，因此每
message I get will cause this to
我收到的消息将导致
anchormen I'm also defining another
主持人，我也在定义另一个
counter only this one is messages but it
反击这只是消息，但它
points in the actual event hostname
指向实际事件的主机名
consume them in this way it'll take the
以这种方式食用它们将需要
message counts and split them between
邮件计数并在它们之间分配
the host name and this will tabulate it
主机名，并将其制成表格
up I'm going to pause and
我要暂停一下
excellent slack here just not disturb us
出色的懈怠不打扰我们
anymore okay so that's what is on the
好的，所以这就是
right side we're going to count what was
右边，我们要数一下
consumed now let's look at the left-hand
现在消耗掉，让我们看看左侧
side this simulator that's generating
这个模拟器的侧面
traffic help at the top you know I have
您知道我有顶部的交通帮助
another counter service object and I you
另一个柜台服务对象，我
know I plugged it into the constructor
知道我将其插入构造函数
call here
叫这里
down at the bottom you know we have the
在底部，你知道我们有
this is our code we had all along to
这是我们一直以来的代码
send the message out over JMS or the JMS
通过JMS或JMS发送消息
temple but here have added a couple
寺庙，但这里增加了一对
increment operations on the production
生产上的增量操作
side so here we have messages total dot
一边，所以这里我们有消息总点
produced and then we also do the same
生产，然后我们也做同样的事情
break it out by host names
按主机名划分
okay well I'll set here let's let's fire
好吧，我在这里设置让我们开火
up this version of the demo get it going
这个演示版本开始
okay pause the output you know at a
好吧，暂停您知道的输出
glance
扫视
same sort of thing running on Tomcat
在Tomcat上运行的同类事物
port 8080 you know traffic we see the
端口8080，您知道流量，我们看到了
same simulated traffic being generated
产生相同的模拟流量
we're going to do is go over to the
我们要做的是转到
browser and look at the metrics endpoint
浏览器并查看指标端点
so here we actually have a lot of
所以在这里我们实际上有很多
metrics already predefined by
指标已由预先定义
spring-green actuator so if we look down
Spring 绿色的执行器，如果我们往下看
here at the bottom we can see the custom
在底部，我们可以看到自定义
ones that we just talked about down here
我们刚才在这里谈论的那些
so we can see that multiplex 205
所以我们可以看到多路传输205
consumed and produced the router 101
消耗并生产了路由器101
consumed to produce the switch and then
消耗以产生开关，然后
the totals you know here we can you know
您在这里知道的总数我们可以知道
we can sit there and refresh it you know
我们可以坐在那里刷新它，你知道
and some of the stuff you notice down
还有一些你注意到的东西
here there's also counters for this one
这里也有这个柜台
right here is telling us when we hit end
就在这里告诉我们何时结束
point metrics and we get a 200 code
点指标，我们得到200个代码
which is hitting the webpage we're
正在访问我们正在访问的网页
looking at the stage has been loaded up
看着舞台已经装了
four times in this case we're talking
在这种情况下我们谈论了四次
about you know plug it in some custom
关于你知道的将其插入一些自定义
counters counters increment and decrease
计数器计数器递增和递减
with what gauges do a gauge has a gauge
仪表有什么规格
has a fixed value and every time you
具有固定值，每次您
update a gauge you updated with a new
用新的更新您更新的量规
value so it's like looking at a gauge on
值，就像在看一个量表
on a car where at any one time you're
在任何时候都在的汽车上
looking at what's the current readout of
看一下什么是当前的读数
that am i driving it at 50 miles an hour
那是我以每小时50英里的速度驾驶它
am i driving it at 80 kilometers an hour
我以每小时80公里的速度开车吗
that kind of thing the gauge is always
量规总是这样的事情
updating itself some value and in that
更新自身的价值，
situation cannot be as interested in
情况可能不那么感兴趣
what it was five minutes ago so you can
五分钟前是什么，所以你可以
inject both counter services and gauge
注入柜台服务和量具
services to do that now by default
现在默认情况下会执行此操作的服务
spring mood actuator is writing this
春天的心情促动器正在写这篇
stuff to an in-memory instance and in
内存实例和内部
the memory metric repository
内存指标存储库
so essentially you know it writes it
所以基本上你知道它写
locally and it's very handy to get going
在本地，出发非常方便
but when you run into situations like
但是当您遇到诸如
deployment to production and having four
部署到生产中并拥有四个
instances you're going to have each
您将拥有的每个实例
instance it's going to have its own
实例将有自己的
metrics the common situation we start
衡量我们开始的常见情况
talking about twelve fact or
谈论十二个事实或
applications and production is you want
您想要的应用程序和生产
all four instances to type this metric
所有四个实例以键入此指标
data to a third-party collector and in
数据发送给第三方收集器
this case spring loot actuator actually
这种情况下Spring 战利品执行器实际上
has a Redis metric repository so it's
有一个Redis指标存储库，因此
possible to in your application you can
在您的应用程序中可以
go define a redis metric repository beam
去定义一个Redis度量库光束
and you can qualify it with a profile
您可以通过个人资料来限定它
that when you go to cloud deployment use
在您进行云部署时
the Redis metric repository instead at
Redis指标存储库，而不是位于
the end memory one and then all
最终记忆一个然后全部
instances are going to bind with that
实例将与此绑定
instance of Raddatz that you link to it
您链接到它的Raddatz实例
spring boot has a metric repository
Spring Boot具有度量标准存储库
auto-configuration
自动配置
and based on what we've learned and
根据我们所学到的
looking at auto configuration settings
查看自动配置设置
when I look at this thing right here
当我在这里看这个东西时
that says that here's a configuration of
那表示这是一个配置
being definition in this case a single
在这种情况下被定义为一个
bean and in metric an in-memory metric
Bean和公制内存中公制
repository and it is can only happens if
存储库，只有在以下情况下才会发生
there is no metric repository so if
没有度量标准存储库，所以如果
nobody is to find any metric repository
没有人可以找到任何度量标准存储库
create this so if you go create a Redis
创建这个，所以如果你去创建一个Redis
metric repository when you deploy to
部署到以下度量标准存储库
cloud it will make boot back off of this
云，它将使启动从此退出
one and use the other one instead
一个并使用另一个
but there's other opportunity by the
但还有其他机会
Tauri interface and have that kick in
Tauri界面并加入
and write your stuff to a database with
并将您的资料写入数据库
spring data or you can write it out over
春天的数据，或者你可以写出来
a channel to some external third-party
通往某些外部第三方的渠道
things
东西
now the last thing I want to get into
现在我想进入的最后一件事
here is we call crash support crash as
这就是我们所谓的崩溃支持崩溃
an interesting name crash is a remote
一个有趣的名字崩溃是一个远程
shell tool that you that you can link up
您可以链接的shell工具
to your applications but it does it
到您的应用程序，但是可以做到
comes with several commands and metrics
带有一些命令和指标
and features out of the box but spring
和功能开箱即用，但春天
boot actuator adds support to write your
引导执行器增加了对编写驱动器的支持
own commands in this case we're going to
在这种情况下，我们将使用自己的命令
write some ones for activemq that close
写一些关闭的activemq
this box down here so this is the whole
这个盒子在这里，所以这是整个
code for my activemq command that i'm
我的我的activemq命令的代码
going to register the crash I'm going to
要记录我要去的崩溃
talk about what this does and then we'll
谈论这是做什么的，然后我们将
actually go login to crash which is
实际上去登录崩溃
attached to our running application and
附加到我们正在运行的应用程序，并
see what it looks like this code is all
看看这段代码看起来像什么
written in groovy so it's real terse now
用groovy编写，所以现在很简洁
because these turn into commands we defy
因为这些变成了我们无视的命令
some of the standard Java formatting
一些标准的Java格式
rules like notices classes all lowercase
通知类之类的规则全部小写
that's because this is a primary commit
那是因为这是主要的提交
this is going to be registered as a
这将被注册为
primary command and I don't want to be
主要命令，我不想成为
typing mixed case on the command line
在命令行上输入大小写混合
now each of these function definitions
现在，每个这些功能定义
are you know what I would call a sub
你知道我会怎么称呼潜艇吗
command so we're going to define ping
命令，所以我们要定义ping
and metrics notice it's flagged as a
和指标注意到它被标记为
command each of these gets access to the
命令每个都可以访问
invocation context and this means we can
调用上下文，这意味着我们可以
look up about anything we need the case
查找我们需要的任何情况
we have access to fetch a spring bean
我们可以取回Spring bean
factory and that's the ticket to looking
工厂，那是寻找的门票
up any spring beans so down here I'm
上任何Spring bean ，所以我在这里
going to fetch the connection factory
将获取连接工厂
and basically do the same check that I
基本上做同样的检查
showed in that other Java code only here
仅在此处显示其他Java代码中
it's doing in a different it's doing a
它在做不同的事情
create connection call but instead of
创建连接呼叫，而不是
returning a health indicator it just
返回一个健康指标
returns a plain string broker is up but
返回一个纯字符串代理，但是
if it throws an exception return brokers
如果抛出异常，则返回经纪人
down down here is my other sub command
这里是我的另一个子命令
metrics so in this case I'm going to
指标，在这种情况下，我要
fetch the bean factory and fish out the
取 bean 工厂并捞出
metric repository what this does is this
指标存储库这是什么
lets me get a hold of all
让我掌握一切
metrics at once in this case I'm going
在这种情况下，一次
to use a little groovy collection magic
使用一些时髦的魔术
find all metrics iterate over them and
找到所有度量对其进行迭代，然后
that the metric mean starts with counter
指标均值以计数器开头
dot messages let's just print the name
点信息让我们只打印名称
and the value at the screen now it's
现在屏幕上的值是
possible here to use a groovy find
可能在这里使用常规查找
operation nowadays I'm greeting this to
如今的操作，我在此问候
kind of merge these two ops together but
将这两个操作合并在一起，但是
let's so let's search this is a nice
让我们搜索一下，这是一个不错的选择
efficient way to write some small
小写的有效方法
support commands
支持命令
I believe the whole thing is running
我相信整个事情都在运行
someone an exit presentation mode and go
有人退出演示模式，然后去
over to my command line and log in to
转到我的命令行并登录
crash
崩溃
now crash what crash doesn't let us
现在崩溃什么崩溃不会让我们
login it's by SSH and its default is to
通过SSH登录，默认为
run on port 2000 on the machine and I
在机器上的端口2000上运行，我
believe it only by default supports
相信只有默认支持
local access now I'm logged in and I'm
本地访问，现在我已登录，并且
looking at the crash and I'm going to
看着车祸，我要去
type help
输入帮助
what kind of do is list all the commands
列出所有命令是做什么的
that are available there's there's a lot
那里有很多
of built-in commands to that you can
内置命令，您可以
explore there could be a whole session
探索可能会有整个会议
and of itself but I'm just going to go
本身，但我只是去
look at the academic you command that I
看看你命令我
defined so here gives me a readout
定义所以这里给我一个读出
saying well you have this nitrix command
说得好，你有这个nitrox命令
and a ping command and this is where the
和ping命令，这是
document rack that usage annotations
使用说明的文件架
allow me to control the the information
让我控制信息
that's posted here so you know in one
张贴在这里，所以你知道一个
fell swoop I was able to put both metric
我能够把两个指标
data and health data all into one root
数据和健康数据全部集中到一个根
command ActiveMQ and getting readout on
命令ActiveMQ并获取读数
this stuff
这个东西
and honest if I shut down the broker I
老实说，如果我关闭经纪人，我
can go back here do another you know do
可以回到这里做另一个你知道的事
another thing and now it tells me the
另一件事，现在它告诉我
broker is down so it's just another way
经纪人破产了，这是另一种方式
to get a readout I started active in
为了获得读数，我开始活跃于
queue back up you can check now it's
排队备份，您可以检查一下
back up
备份
so let's recap these non-functional
因此，让我们回顾一下这些不起作用的
features that we have we have an auto
我们拥有的功能
configuration report we wrote some
配置报告我们写了一些
custom health checks we had application
我们申请的自定义健康检查
information custom metrics custom crash
信息自定义指标自定义崩溃
commands mixed up together in fact
实际上，命令混在一起
there's even more than that when it
甚至还有更多
comes to non-functional and well that's
变成无功能的，那是
a good point I maybe I should stop
好一点，我也许应该停止
saying non-functional I've actually
说我实际上没有功能
confessed to you I've never really liked
向你坦白我从没真正喜欢过
the expression non-functional because it
该表达式无功能，因为它
sounds like it doesn't do anything and
听起来好像什么也没做
to me the stuff does a lot so I prefer
对我来说东西很多，所以我更喜欢
referring to these things as like op
将这些东西称为op
support features instead of
支持功能而不是
non-functional features so the code that
非功能性的功能，代码
you write to support you know your
你写信来支持你知道你的
business functionality doesn't your
业务功能不是您的
business needs and then these tools help
业务需求，然后这些工具帮助
support op stuff one thing you know we
支持运维一件事，你知道我们
talked about like for instance putting
谈到像放
metric stuff in in this example it was
在这个例子中，度量指标是
very simple and contrived there are only
非常简单，人为的
two points of message traffic happening
发生两点消息通信
so you know it's hand coded in a real
所以你知道它是手工编码的
production system I would look at using
我将使用的生产系统
something like Springs aspect-oriented
像Springs面向方面的东西
programming support and possibly writing
编程支持和可能的写作
a piece of advice to hook in you know
一条忠告你知道的建议
tap into key points where I want to
挖掘我想要的关键点
collect metrics on the data that's
收集有关数据的指标
flowing through the system and then you
流过系统，然后您
know in in a production environment if I
知道在生产环境中是否
have you know if I've scaled up to four
你知道我是否扩大到四个
instances or 100 hundred instances I
实例或十亿个实例
would like to bind that to a rate a
想要将其绑定到速率a
Redis service and pipe all the metrics
Redis服务并传递所有指标
into that solution there and be able to
那里的解决方案，并能够
go analyze it after the fact but to with
去事实之后去分析它
spring a boot and all the support it's
靴子和所有的支持
it's very easy and fun to go build this
建立这个非常简单有趣
stuff without doing a lot of low-level
没有做很多低级的东西
plumbing so to put a wrap on things I
水暖，所以要包裹我的东西
did want to remind everybody there's
确实想提醒大家
still time to sign up for spring 1/2 GX
还有时间报名参加1/2 GX春天
this September which I want to be
我想成为今年九月
speaking at it about spring date arrest
谈论春季逮捕
data needs hypermedia plus security so
数据需要超媒体和安全性，因此
I'd encourage everybody to sign up as
我鼓励大家注册成为
possible
可能
and with that we conclude our
并以此得出结论
presentation we'll see if Peters got any
演示文稿，我们将看看Peters有没有
questions for us yeah definitely a bunch
对我们的问题肯定是一堆
of stuff coming in for
的东西进来
audience a number of people I think we I
观众很多人，我想我们我
think you addressed this throughout the
认为您在整个过程中都解决了这个问题
course of the presentation but I just
演讲过程中，但我只是
want to make sure a couple people were
想要确保有几个人
thrown off by your sort of VM colon
被您的VM冒号抛弃
backslash backslash localhost and we
反斜杠反斜杠localhost和我们
everyone thinks that you were referring
每个人都以为你指的是
to the internal activemq broker with
到内部activemq经纪人
that URL syntax is that correct yeah
URL语法是正确的
that is that is active nq's noted but
那是活跃的nq的记录，但
they they have a broker URL and if
他们有经纪人网址，如果
you're using embedded that is the format
您使用的是嵌入式格式
when they specify embedded internal
当他们指定嵌入式内部
broker it will be M : / / localhost but
经纪人它将是M /// localhost但
okay so that's that that's that
好的，那就是那样
in-memory flag that you were studying
您正在学习的内存中标志
right yeah you go in and set the we need
是的，您进入并设置我们需要的
when you flip flop the in-memory flag
当您触发器内存中标志时
that's what it will configure it will
这就是它将配置的内容
configure the embedded broker and the
配置嵌入式代理和
meta broker that's the URL that it uses
元代理是它使用的URL
to as an indicator that what Springwood
以指示什么Springwood
does if you flip the flag to fall so
如果您将旗帜倒下会怎样
don't use in memory it will try to go
不要在内存中使用它将尝试
guess them what it should connect to and
猜他们应该连接到什么
it will default to its standard port
它将默认使用其标准端口
number and go looking for it there but
数字，然后去那里寻找
if you stand up ActiveMQ and you're
如果您站起来ActiveMQ而您
using a non-standard port or it's on
使用非标准端口或已打开
another machine not on you're not on
您不在的另一台机器不在
localhost then you will have to figure
本地主机，那么你将不得不图
the broker URL property directly to tell
经纪人URL属性直接告诉
it where that instance is got it okay
它在那个实例得到的地方还可以
thanks um so yes that was one question
谢谢，所以是的，这是一个问题
let's see duty duty to do yeah Carol
让我们来看看有责任做的事卡罗尔
Carol asks which let's see yeah okay
卡罗尔问，让我们看看是的
sorry that was the same question she was
抱歉，这是她同样的问题
she was asking about the activemq thing
她在问activemq的事情
um
嗯
Christopher Smith was asking if that can
克里斯托弗·史密斯（Christopher Smith）问是否可以
does that connection get closed
该连接是否关闭
automatically I'm not sure what
自动我不确定
specifically he was talking about at
特别是他在谈论
that moment in time it was about 10:30
那一刻大约是10:30
was about 10 26 so I think we kind of
大约是10月26日，所以我觉得我们有点
lost the context on that one a little
在那一点上失去了背景
bit but well I'm gonna heads all of this
有点，但是我要负责所有这一切
and say that you know my mechanism here
说你知道我的机制
was I was using
我在用吗
ActiveMQ is the means to demonstrate
ActiveMQ是演示的方法
some configuration settings I was
我当时的一些配置设置
killing and restarting an app which may
终止并重新启动可能会
not be the cleanest way to detach from a
并不是分离的最干净方法
broker configuration so you know you're
经纪人配置，所以您知道自己
running if you're going to stop and
如果您要停止运行
start things or shutting down the broker
开始事情或关闭经纪人
the way I did in the middle of things it
我在事物中间做的方式
raises the idea of well we're any
提出了我们是任何人的想法
messages lost there where the messages
消息丢失在那里消息
supposed to not be lost what how do you
应该不会丢失你怎么办
hedge against that
对冲
to where well the brokers down let me
经纪人让我失望的地方
stop all the messages until the brokers
停止所有消息，直到经纪人
back up none of that's covered in the
备份所有这些都没有
context of the demo I was doing and
我正在演示的上下文
there's something you need to design for
您需要设计一些东西
but you know you it's it's the same kind
但你知道你是同一种
of thing to look at if you were to use
要使用的东西
RabbitMQ you have to evaluate that kind
RabbitMQ，您必须进行评估
of stuff or whatever whatever you're
东西或其他任何东西
using in your application you can find
在您的应用程序中使用您可以找到
you can find without a configuration
您无需配置即可找到
report the the bits of code that spring
报告那个春天的代码片段
move uses to activate automatic means
移动使用来激活自动方式
for you awesome okay cool let's see Marc
给你很棒，好酷，让我们看看马克
asks hey Greg you don't specify the
问嘿格雷格，您没有指定
version numbers in the Gradle file how
Gradle文件中的版本号如何
do you know what versions the libraries
你知道图书馆的版本吗
are used then and can you override it
然后使用，您可以覆盖它吗
conversion can a use version
转换可以使用的版本
automatically change behind your back
自动改变你的身后
like for example if a new version of the
例如，如果新版本的
library is released that is a great
库发布了，很棒
question um let me see here I like to
问题um让我看看这里我喜欢
keep it out of presentational because it
使其脱离表现形式，因为它
won't show this stuff but I'm
不会显示这些东西，但是我
highlighting that I'm trying to tell you
强调我想告诉你
what you're seeing here at the top is
您在顶部看到的是
where I specify spring boot Gradle
我在哪里指定Spring Boot Gradle
plugin and this one has a version number
插件，这个有一个版本号
this is 1.2.3.4 spring boot comes with a
这是1.2.3.4 Spring Boot随附的
predefined set of versions for all these
所有这些的预定义版本集
for these particular dependencies down
对于这些特定的依赖关系
here so in my IDE I can scroll down and
在这里，所以在我的IDE中，我可以向下滚动
see exactly which versions that pull
确切地看到哪个版本
down I'm highlighting the spring boot
我强调 spring boot
starters they all have one two three
初学者，他们都有一二三
release on them but down under the hood
在他们身上释放但在引擎盖下
I can glean that like here's it's using
我可以像这里使用的那样收集
spring framework four one six release
Spring Framework 四一六发布
you know and with that there's
你知道，有
it picks the other dependencies up but
它选择了其他依赖项，但
you're at you know this is sort of the
你在，你知道这有点
default situation but you can actually
默认情况，但实际上
go in and override a property setting or
进入并覆盖属性设置或
sorry overwrite a version number you
抱歉，您覆盖了一个版本号
know if I I wanted to change it I can do
知道我是否想改变它我可以做
that and there's a different way to do
那有另一种方法
it if you happen to be using maven so
如果您碰巧正在使用Maven，那么
I'm going to click the built the Gradle
我要单击内置的Gradle
file there and change the spring boot
文件在那里并更改 spring boot
actuator to be 1.2 got to release
执行器要释放到1.2
instead of 1.2.3 now I give it a second
而不是1.2.3现在我再说一遍
here
这里
now here's where I may be slightly
现在在这里我可能会稍微
mistaken on how to tweak property I know
弄错了我知道如何调整财产
how to I know how to change the property
我怎么知道如何改变财产
numbers very easily with mazey
mazey很容易就能得到数字
it may even you're able to override it
甚至您都可以覆盖它
through a property settings
通过属性设置
but I would have to go look up precisely
但我必须去精确地抬头
how that is done with with Gradle
如何用Gradle完成
so like is an amazing configuration
就像是一个了不起的配置
there there's basically a property
基本上有一个属性
setting for each of those things like
为诸如此类的事物设置
there's a Java version setting for boot
有一个用于启动的Java版本设置
you know this is this is a totally
你知道这是完全
different app than what we're looking at
与我们正在寻找的应用程序不同
but there's a property called spring hey
但是有一个叫做春天的财产
do stock version because this app is
做股票版本，因为这个程序是
using Springs hey deels project and here
使用Springs Hey Deels项目以及此处
I can plug this in to change the version
我可以插入它来更改版本
that boots going to use and there's a
靴子要用，还有一个
property for each for each of the key
每个键的每个属性
libraries but I'm not a speed on how to
图书馆，但我对如何
override that flag in Gradle but it
在Gradle中覆盖该标志，但它
should be mentioned in the reference
应该在参考中提到
documents and it's the version numbers
文档及其版本号
are not going to change under the hood
不会改变
because that's part of the screen boots
因为那是屏幕启动的一部分
release the only time that that would be
释放那唯一的时间
an issue and some you know so here's
一个问题，有些你知道，所以这是
what the version numbers pick you can go
您可以选择哪个版本号
look up this version in github there's a
在github中查找此版本
tag on one two three release and you can
在一二三发布上标记，您可以
look up exactly what the version numbers
查找确切的版本号
are go with that the only time they're
与他们一起唯一的时间
going to change is if you happen to be
要改变的是，如果你碰巧是
using the snapshot release and they're
使用快照版本，它们是
they could be fumbling with the versions
他们可能会摸索版本
if i zoom in button here zoom in on this
如果我放大按钮在这里放大
a little bit perfect looks good spring
春季看起来有点完美
mood dependencies pom dot XML this is
心情依赖性pom点XML这是
where all the version numbers and their
所有版本号及其
property overrides are behind I notice
我注意到背后的属性覆盖
you know this is a fixed thing and so
你知道这是固定的，所以
when you have a specific conversion the
当您进行特定转换时
numbers aren't going to change under the
数字不会改变
hood right yeah boots boots sort of bill
胡德权利是靴子靴子法案
of materials is going to hand you a
材料将使您
specific cut of things right now and
现在具体的事情和
it's not going to get squirrely on you
不会撒娇
unless there's a new boot release or you
除非有新的启动版本，否则您
know maybe if you're using the spring
知道也许你在用Spring
i/o platform maven bill of materials you
I / O平台Maven物料清单
know that that's another indication
知道那是另一个迹象
that's another chin that's another
这是另一个下巴，另一个
opportunity for the version numbers to
版本号的机会
potentially be different but um yeah
可能会有所不同，但是嗯
yeah yep yeah cool okay I think we I
是的，是的，很酷，我想我们
think we got that um Christopher Smith
认为我们得到了那个克里斯托弗·史密斯
asks you know warning possibly off topic
问您是否知道警告可能偏离主题
but is there any way to get crash on
但是有什么办法让崩溃
Cloud Foundry
云铸造
on a cloud foundry application I think
我认为在云铸造应用程序上
that's an interesting question I don't
这不是我一个有趣的问题
know if you have any insight into that
知道您是否对此有任何见识
one I know I don't but um oh gosh I had
我知道我不是，但是哦，天哪，我有
a tunnel like that so I haven't I
这样的隧道，所以我没有
haven't tunnel that because I realize it
并没有因为我意识到
should if you were to upload this app to
如果您要将这个应用程序上传到
Cloud Foundry it should be running but I
Cloud Foundry它应该正在运行，但是我
don't know you would have to have that
不知道你必须要那个
port exported to the out oh yeah that
端口出口到外面哦，是的
won't work yet then um where there's
将无法正常工作，然后在哪里
actually there's an upcoming release
实际上会有一个即将发布的版本
with the Diego release we will be
随着Diego版本的发布，我们将
supporting SSH so that you can do port
支持SSH，以便您可以进行端口
forwarding and that would allow you to
转发，这将使您能够
use crash yep that's a good thing and
使用崩溃是一件好事，
SSH in your when you're trying to SSH
尝试SSH时使用SSH
into your production system as always
一如既往地进入您的生产系统
you know double check that that's the
你知道仔细检查一下
right solution you want to do yes
您想做的正确解决方案
yep well you know we all need to you
是的，你知道我们都需要你
know we all need to sometimes
知道我们有时候都需要
troubleshoot you know configuration
解决您知道的配置问题
mismatches between you know dev and you
您知道开发人员与您之间的不匹配
know staging and production so there's
知道演出和制作，所以有
that but yeah interesting
那但是是有趣的
so Chris hopefully that that kind of
所以克里斯希望那种
answers that hopefully that addresses
希望能解决的答案
your question there a couple of other
您的问题还有另外两个
questions actually a lot of other
其实还有很多其他问题
questions
问题
so ROM asks how do you start and stop a
因此ROM询问您如何启动和停止
boot application via the configuration
通过配置启动应用程序
okay there is a there is actually a
好吧，实际上有一个
shutdown end point
关机终点
okay we see where is that camera head
好吧，我们看到那个摄像头在哪里
yeah there's an endpoint you can curl
是的，你可以弯腰
against this is what they're talking
他们正在说反对
about these end points that I mentioned
关于我提到的这些终点
we saw them like we looked at Auto
我们看到他们就像看着汽车一样
config we looked at config props we
配置我们看了配置道具我们
looked at health info we looked at
看了我们看过的健康信息
metrics there's another endpoint called
指标还有另一个端点
shutdown you can send a request to you
关闭，您可以向您发送请求
it is it is disabled by default it's the
默认情况下它是禁用的
probably right for several reasons you
可能由于以下几个原因而正确
know you don't want to accidentally open
知道你不想意外打开
the way for people to kill your app so
人们杀死您的应用程序的方式
but you can enable it and there's also
但您可以启用它，还有
the option to have all these these are
所有这些选项都是
called management endpoints there's a
称为管理端点
option to have the management endpoints
具有管理端点的选项
also protected by spring security with a
也受到Spring 安全性的保护
username password that the admins would
管理员将使用的用户名密码
have so recommendation is if you are
有这样的建议是，如果你是
going to have this turned on you want to
要打开这个，你想
protected behind security so people
受安全保护，使人们
can't ask it but once the application is
不能问，但一旦申请
shut down then there's nobody to send a
关闭然后没有人发送
request to to start it up so in that
要求启动它，这样
case you know you have to fire up either
如果你知道你必须开火
gonna have to launch the app yourself
必须自己启动该应用
you know on the command line or if
你知道在命令行上还是
you're using something like Cloud
你正在使用像云之类的东西
Foundry that you have stop and start
铸造厂，你已经停下脚步了
buttons from inside via Oh Greg I'm
通过哦格雷格从内部按钮我是
going to stop you for one second sorry
要阻止你一秒钟抱歉
if one or two people are asking for a
如果一两个人要
brief description of Cloud Foundry so
Cloud Foundry的简要说明
for anyone that's in familiar Cloud
对于熟悉Cloud的任何人
Foundry is a platform as a service there
铸造是平台即服务
we what Greg is showing you right now is
我们格雷格现在向您展示的是
the console for pivotal Web Services
关键Web服务的控制台
that is a instance of Cloud Foundry that
这是Cloud Foundry的一个实例
we run on top of Amazon Web Services
我们在Amazon Web Services之上运行
that's sort of our public cloud you
有点像我们的公共云
might compare it to a Heroku or
可能会将其与Heroku或
something like that you know has
你知道有类似的东西
excellent spring support excellent
极好的Spring 支持
spring boot support um you know just
spring boot 支持你知道
fantastic Java build pack
很棒的Java构建包
experience and this is a you know a
经验，这是你知道的
platform as a service you as a developer
平台即服务，您作为开发者
basically are you know you tell you tell
基本上你知道你告诉你告诉
cloud sundar how many instances you want
cloud sundar您想要多少个实例
how much memory you want and it will
您想要多少内存，它将
create a fleet of managed virtual
创建一组托管虚拟
machines or Linux containers that will
机器或Linux容器
you know manage your application
你知道管理你的申请
lifecycle for you yeah
是你的生命周期
but tons more than that but
但比那更多
go check it out at a pivotal day oh
关键的一天去看看哦
there's an overview of Cloud Foundry
概述了Cloud Foundry
there I'm sorry about that crack I just
我为那个裂缝感到抱歉
wanted to level set so that people maybe
想水平设置，以便人们
people weren't lost yes I don't know
人们没有迷路，是的，我不知道
what it was yeah so you can't go make a
是的，所以你不能去做一个
web request to an app that's not running
Web请求到未运行的应用程序
so in this case you know here I have
所以在这种情况下，你知道我在这里
this my demo app it's going to be at
这是我的演示应用程序，它将在
spring one and it's running on pivotal
春天一，它在关键
Web Services and you know here I have a
Web服务，您知道我这里有一个
stop button or a restart button and I
停止按钮或重启按钮，我
can start it up because it's my instance
可以启动它，因为这是我的实例
in the cloud you know to run this app so
在云中，您知道要运行此应用程序，因此
if you come and find up you get to find
如果你来找，你会发现
out how to post your own pictures from
了解如何发布自己的图片
your iPhone of take pictures of cats put
您的iPhone拍下猫的照片
it on the web like everyone else does so
像其他人一样在网络上
you got a got another question oh yeah
你还有另一个问题哦，是的
sorry sorry I was just cut and pasting
抱歉，抱歉，我只是剪切粘贴
some some answers into the chat window
聊天窗口中的一些答案
um let's see the guy that was asking
嗯，让我们看看问的那个人
about the start and stop boot
关于启动和停止引导
application also was commenting that app
应用程序也在评论该应用程序
top properties sort of has a toggle but
顶级属性有点拨动但
anyway
无论如何
Christopher Smith's question earlier
克里斯托弗·史密斯（Christopher Smith）先前的问题
about the connection getting closed
关于连接即将关闭
automatically that was regarding the
自动是关于
health indicator he was saying that you
他说你的健康指标
know hey checks whether it can open a
知道嘿检查它是否可以打开一个
connection and then returns up or down
连接，然后向上或向下返回
and he was curious if that connection
他很好奇那联系
gets closed automatically do you happen
会自动关闭吗
to know that one actually that's a good
知道实际上这是一件好事
question the I would actually it to look
问题我实际上会看起来
at the semantics of it but that's
在它的语义上，但这是
actually something then sure you're
其实是什么，然后确定你是
doing proper resource management and I
做适当的资源管理，我
did not actually look heavily at that
其实并没有认真看
okay so you
好的，所以你
you know interests a arguably I need to
你知道利益可以说我需要
read but boot your your your potentially
阅读但引导您的潜在
adding something here to to clean up the
在这里添加一些东西来清理
connection so so that's the thing yeah
连接，所以就是这样
okay got it so you you have to attend to
好吧，所以你必须参加
that programmatically yourself boot
以编程方式自己启动
doesn't automatically clean up that
不会自动清理
connection no boots really not aware of
连接没有靴子真的不知道
this custom code you know that you have
您知道这个自定义代码
to make sure that you close that kind of
确保您关闭了
stuff you know if I guess theoretically
从理论上讲，你知道的东西
with only it's only going to clean it up
只有它只会清理它
if it properly goes out of scope right
如果它正确地超出了范围，对不对
as folks oh that's a good question are
作为乡亲哦，这是一个很好的问题是
you doing proper resource cleanup so I
你在做适当的资源清理，所以我
wouldn't okay I would go check and make
不行，我去检查一下
sure to do that correctly so they have a
一定要正确地做，所以他们有一个
good point on that okay um excellent um
好的，很好，很好
let's see Mohammed asks how does the
让我们看看穆罕默德（Mohammed）问
ping and metrics options appear on the
ping和指标选项显示在
shelf or ActiveMQ okay um we pull that
架子或ActiveMQ好吧，我们拉一下
script up basically okay what this
脚本基本上可以，这是什么
script is located in the source main
脚本位于源主目录中
resources slash commands so step one is
资源斜线命令，所以第一步是
on the X out of presentation mode so I
在X的演示模式之外，所以我
can see the ax project view so this is
可以看到斧头项目视图，所以这是
the path where it needs to be any groovy
需要任何常规的路径
file down here underneath the commands
在命令下方将文件归档
folder in this case I can include
在这种情况下，我可以包含文件夹
grooving will be scanned by boot to be
开槽将被引导扫描为
cert to be linked with the crash support
与崩溃支持链接的证书
and then on top of that it's going to it
然后最重要的是
probably will just grab it if it's class
如果是上课的话，可能会抓住它
stuff but it needs to see like the app
的东西，但它需要看起来像应用程序
command annotation Flags this method is
命令注释标记此方法为
actually being a command this way you
实际上是这样的命令
know you can define you may need other
知道你可以定义你可能需要其他
methods etc in here too if it gets more
如果有更多的方法也可以在这里
complex but that you can this is where
复杂，但是你可以在这里
you define the text material that is
您定义的文字材料是
showing up there with these annotations
这些注释在那里出现
and finally you know comes with some
最后你知道来了一些
built-in man pages for each command so
每个命令的内置手册页
and there's a lot of details on write
而且有很多关于写的细节
this code in the reference documents but
该代码在参考文件中，但是
these are
这些是
piecing together from the reference
从参考文献拼凑而成
documents is one thing but being able to
文件是一回事，但能够
see an actual assembled example I think
看到一个我认为的实际组装示例
is really nice and this is this is code
真的很好，这是代码
I've lifted right out of chapter 3 of my
我已经从我的第3章中解脱出来
book
书
awesome got it um okay
很棒，很好
Gillette asks hey is there a preference
吉列问嘿有偏好吗
for deploying as a jar as opposed to a
用于部署为罐子，而不是
war in production and if so why you know
生产战争，如果是这样，为什么你知道
this is the you know fat jar question I
这是你知道的胖子罐问题
think yeah there's you know there's a
认为是的，你知道有一个
growing interest in using ether jars
对使用乙醚罐的兴趣与日俱增
whatever essentially which in this case
在这种情况下基本上是什么
spring boot has its own loader the the
spring boot 有自己的装载机
jar standard itself from Java doesn't
Java本身的jar标准本身
support runnable jars which comedians
支持喜剧演员的可运行罐子
always been weird
一直很奇怪
so spring lumen puts a jar loader in
所以春天的流明放了一个罐子装载器
there and it puts in each tendency as a
在那里，它把每种趋势作为
jar file itself I've seen other uber jar
jar文件本身，我见过其他超级jar
solutions
解决方案
unpack jar files and put all the class
解压缩jar文件并放入所有类
files in there and you may be a risk of
文件在那里，您可能会有
overlap stuff and or you might be a risk
重叠的东西，否则您可能会有风险
of license violation but trundle up in
违反许可证，但陷入困境
the jars I think it's handy but more
我认为这很方便，但更多
files are really aimed for one thing and
文件确实是针对一件事的，
one thing only and that's to deploy to
只有一件事，那就是部署到
containers to app servers or they you
应用服务器的容器或它们
know can deploy it to Tomcat the jar
知道可以将其部署到Tomcat的jar中
files are really designed to work
文件确实是可以正常工作的
anywhere when you use them with boots
当你在靴子上使用它们的任何地方
it's just a Java jar you know my at that
那只是一个Java jar，你知道我在那
jar so I think a lot of people have
罐子，所以我想很多人都有
adopted that and when you use tools like
当您使用诸如
cloud foundry uh it's very easy to go
cloud Foundry嗯，这很容易
you know you can push a jar up there and
你知道你可以把一个罐子推到那里
you know you it may look like it's about
你知道你可能看起来像是关于
the same thing but you know War Powers
同样的事情，但你知道战争力量
that have typically tend to be
通常倾向于
associated with containers but it is
与容器相关联，但是
possible to make an executable war file
可以制作可执行的war文件
but the default position of boot is when
但是启动的默认位置是
you use the spring glue plug in whether
您是否使用Spring 胶塞
it's maven or Gradle it's it will build
它是Maven或Gradle，它将建立
you an executable jar file
您是一个可执行的jar文件
cool sorry I got stuck on mute there for
很抱歉，我在那儿陷入了静音
a second um let's see
一秒钟，让我们来看看
question from Vaught s'en he was asking
他问的沃特森的问题
you know how does Cloud Foundry add to
您知道Cloud Foundry如何添加到
boot and I was in the middle of
引导，我在中间
responding I was just basically telling
回应我只是在说
him that you know Cloud Foundry provides
他知道Cloud Foundry提供的他
a kind of public or a private cloud
一种公共云或私有云
deployment environment deployment
部署环境部署
platform for your spring boot apps um
spring boot 应用的平台um
and in fact with the spring cloud
实际上是春天的云
connectors there's actually boot Auto
连接器实际上是启动自动
configurations available for you for
可供您使用的配置
Heroku and for Cloud Foundry services so
Heroku和Cloud Foundry服务，因此
if you're writing an app that you know
如果您正在编写一个知道的应用程序
is going to get deployed on those
将部署在那些
platforms and you're looking to actually
平台，您正在寻找实际
use services that are surfaced through
使用通过以下方式浮出水面的服务
the platform you know much like you
您非常了解的平台
would you know a JDBC connection pool
您知道JDBC连接池吗
you know surface through a container or
你知道通过容器表面或
you know an old-school through through
你知道一所老学校
an app server
应用服务器
you know um that spring Buddha actually
你知道那个春天的佛陀
you know provides auto configurations
你知道提供自动配置
for those services so there's there's a
对于那些服务，所以有一个
there's a lot of value and in boot
有很多的价值，并在启动
specifically on Cloud Foundry in terms
特别是在Cloud Foundry上
of making it easier to work with
使其更易于使用
you know platform provided services and
您知道平台提供的服务和
such I don't know Greg if you want to
这样我不认识格雷格
add to that at all but you know there's
补充一点，但你知道有
others there's another feature that's
其他还有一个功能是
really powerful and it's called the
真的很强大，它被称为
spring profile it's possible to put an
Spring 轮廓，可以把
app profile annotation on on a beam on a
应用配置文件注释在
configuration class and you can have
配置类，您可以拥有
beams only activate when you turn on
光束仅在打开时激活
certain profiles and you can turn on
某些配置文件，您可以打开
more than one profile need to poi an app
一个应用需要多个配置文件
if it's a spring application if you push
如果是春季应用，则按
it up to a Cloud Foundry instance
它直到一个Cloud Foundry实例
whether it's your private copy or you're
无论是您的私人副本还是您
pushing it up to our public physical web
将其推送到我们的公共物理网络
services they automatically put a cloud
他们自动将服务放到云端
profile on your app so it's very easy to
在您的应用程序上进行配置，因此很容易
say well I need this thing to kick in
说好我需要这个东西
when you go to the cloud so I'm going to
当你去云端的时候，我要
put at profile cloud on it and that's an
放在个人资料云上，这是
example where like I was saying you can
比如我说你可以
use the Redis metrics repository and
使用Redis指标存储库并
condition eliza's that only create this
条件伊丽莎的只能创造这个
thing in one
合而为一
goes to the cloud and then I just need
去云，然后我只需要
to be sure that my deployments and it's
确保我的部署及其
bound to an instance of Redis but
绑定到Redis实例，但是
there's also a guide we have here if you
还有一个指南，如果您
go to the spring bio slash guide and
转到春季生物斜线指南，然后
search for lattice what lattices is
搜索晶格是什么晶格
lattices Cloud Foundry with some of the
点阵Cloud Foundry
multi-tenancy features removed from it
从中删除多租户功能
sort of you could say it's lightweight
你可能会说它很轻巧
on requirements but it's still very
根据要求，但仍然非常
powerful on us it's one way to basically
对我们有强大的作用，这是一种基本的方法
run the gist of Cloud Foundry like on
像这样运行Cloud Foundry的要旨
your laptop but run in other places and
您的笔记本电脑，但可以在其他地方运行
this guide actually is sort of an intro
本指南实际上是一个介绍
to using these screen cloud tools that
使用这些屏幕云工具
you're just talking about it's not very
你只是在说那不是很
long to run them on lattice and you know
渴望在晶格上运行它们，你知道
once you get into the clouds to worry
一旦你进入云层担心
you know there's a whole bunch of talks
你知道有很多讲座
there gonna be a spring one to talk
会有一个春天来聊
about the all the components of spring
关于Spring 的所有组成部分
cloud so you make you know
云，让你知道
micro-services and multi unit solutions
微服务和多单元解决方案
out there in the cloud work to get
在云端工作以获得
better to discover each other to do
更好地发现对方要做
things like that so interesting
这样的事情很有趣
interesting related question glen Lingle
有趣的相关问题格伦·林格尔
asks you know to spring buddha's support
问你知道春天佛陀的支持
for high availability with another
与另一个高可用性
machine running for failover and i would
机器运行故障转移，我会
say you know you know not really no I
说你知道你真的不知道我
mean the design point of spring boot is
表示 spring boot 的设计点是
to be a an ultra-light you know
成为超轻量级的
container you know for from
您知道的容器
microservices as greg was just speaking
正如格雷格所说的微服务
about but you know the idea is that you
关于，但你知道的想法是你
know if if we go too far in that
知道我们是否在那方面走得太远
direction you're going to end up with
最终的方向
eventually you're going to end up you
最终你要结束你
know if you go too far in that direction
知道你是否朝那个方向走得太远
you're eventually you know get you know
你最终会知道
hundreds of monkeys sitting at a
数百只猴子坐在
keyboard and you'll end up with IBM
键盘，您最终会遇到IBM
WebSphere right and you know because
WebSphere对，您知道，因为
you're you're you you want to sort of in
你就是你想要的那种
the cloud era I think you you kind of
云时代我想你你有点
want to delegate high availability to
想要将高可用性委托给
the platform that you're running under
您正在运行的平台
as opposed to build that into the App
而不是将其内置到应用程序中
container
容器
I don't know Greg what your comments are
我不知道格雷格，您的评论是什么
but those are those are mine yeah AJ
但是那些是我的啊AJ
stuff is sort of outside the scope of
东西超出了范围
boot you know you can talk about things
启动你知道你可以谈论的事情
like Oracle
像甲骨文
clusters or PostgreSQL clusters or
群集或PostgreSQL群集或
something that you're talking to and
您正在谈论的东西
that's that was something that you'd be
那就是你要做的
setting up outside and so in your
设置在外面等
database configuration you would you
您想要的数据库配置
know configure your boot app to point to
知道配置启动应用程序以指向
the load balancer for that cluster and
该集群的负载均衡器，以及
so boot doesn't need to know anything
所以开机不需要知道任何事情
about that
关于那个
other people have a che requirements
其他人有che的要求
where they need session replication
他们需要会话复制的地方
between multiple instances of Tomcat
Tomcat的多个实例之间
Tomcat has support for doing some of
Tomcat支持执行某些操作
that stuff but like one of their session
这些东西，但就像他们的会议之一
replication features uses multicast and
复制功能使用多播和
if you ever taken multicast into an ops
如果您曾经将多播纳入操作
center you're going to be chased out of
中心，您将被赶出
there because nobody likes multicast
因为没有人喜欢多播
because I've seen I've seen people
因为我见过我见过的人
stand-up multicast solutions and it gets
站立式组播解决方案
out of their data center and takes out
从他们的数据中心取出
800 different data centers because
800个不同的数据中心，因为
somebody didn't understand what they
有人不明白他们在做什么
were doing so the modern cloud solution
正在这样做的现代云解决方案
is is you take your boot app and you
是您拿着启动应用程序，然后
push it up to Cloud Foundry and you spin
将其推到Cloud Foundry，然后旋转
up five instances and Cloud Foundry
五个实例和Cloud Foundry
handle if the load balancing for you it
是否为您处理负载平衡
gives you a URL to talk to whether it's
为您提供一个URL，以讨论是否
they're out of the box one in your
他们开箱即用
registered domain and then it does all
注册域名，然后完成所有工作
the load balancing inside the cloud
云内部的负载平衡
provider and so you don't need to go
提供者，所以您不需要去
fiddle around with that kind of stuff
摆弄这种东西
and then exactly you can also you can
然后你也可以
also stand up you know you can buy into
也站起来，你知道你可以买进
a database service and you let it handle
数据库服务，您让它处理
the high availability requirements and
高可用性要求和
then you don't need to deal with that
那你就不用处理了
from this approach you know but if you
通过这种方法，您知道，但是如果您
you know if you are you know stuck at a
你知道你是否被困在
company that that's working on you know
一直在努力的公司
kind of crusty out server stuff you know
你知道的那种硬皮的服务器东西
then you're you're okay you know then
那你就可以了
you can run boot on a kid on an app
您可以在应用程序上对孩子运行启动
server right and that app and it pops up
服务器权利和该应用程序，它会弹出
and provides some some h.a and failover
并提供一些ha和故障转移
stuff for you
给你的东西
at that level if you know if that's the
在那个水平上，如果你知道那是
environment you're working in so you
您正在工作的环境中
know you can kind of go out of either
知道你可以走出去
way um and now you talk about you you
嗯，现在你在谈论你
can talk to a +4 database server with no
可以与+4数据库服务器通话，而无需
problem you just went it to the load
问题，你只是去负载
balancer or you can go in and configure
平衡器，或者您可以进入并配置
this embedded tomcat server if that's
这个嵌入式的tomcat服务器，如果
what you happen to be using it's we pick
您碰巧正在使用的是我们选择的
a lot of default settings so you don't
许多默认设置，所以您不必
have to but you can go in and declare
必须，但您可以进入并声明
all the settings for Tomcat if needed
Tomcat的所有设置（如果需要）
and turn on that multicast session
并打开该多播会话
replication if that's what you need
如果您需要复制
because I have my book I have a
因为我有书，所以有
demonstration on how to turn on
示范如何开启
an HTTP on Tomcat and have HTTP redirect
Tomcat上的HTTP并具有HTTP重定向
you to the ssl port of that container
您到该容器的ssl端口
automatically but that's something yet
自动，但是那是什么
to do I hand yep excellent yeah last
最后我要做好吗
question I think from Glenn Lingle as
我认为Glenn Lingle提出的问题是
well is there a way to change where the
那么有没有办法改变
commands are like at a specific place on
命令就像在特定位置
the file system I think I'm out I think
我认为文件系统不可用
he's talking about either the CLI or the
他在谈论CLI或
crash I'm not sure if he's talking about
崩溃我不确定他是否在谈论
the like you said about where this file
就像你说的这个文件的位置
goes I'm not sure that that's much sure
我不确定那是肯定的
that's what the question is but oh yeah
这就是问题所在，但是是的
he is just clarifying now I'm over the
他只是在澄清我现在已经结束了
chat window and he is saying crash
聊天窗口，他说当机
command sorry so I think the code has to
命令抱歉，所以我认为代码必须
be here I'm not sure I'm not sure if
在这里我不确定我不确定
that's over writable yet let me see
那太可写了，但让我看看
where it's good yeah it has here is a
那里很好的地方是
this is the default is where it's going
这是默认位置
to look for stuff for commands but you
寻找命令的东西，但是你
can override it by with the pattern
可以用模式覆盖它
machine by setting this property and
通过设置此属性和
application out properties okay okay
应用程序出属性好吧好吧
just about just about everything in boot
几乎所有引导中的内容
that has a setting to it has been
它有一个设置
property is so that it's can be
属性是这样的
overridden so I mean it doesn't you can
覆盖，所以我的意思是你不能
override where application dot
覆盖应用程序点
properties is located or what the name
属性位于或名称
of that properties file is so but this
该属性文件的内容是这样，但这
you know I think this really helps you
你知道我认为这确实对你有帮助
know for people who might be seeing boot
知道可能正在启动的人
for the first time and are and are going
第一次，现在和将来
oh my god like what what just happened
哦，我的上帝喜欢发生了什么
yes you know and and they're they're
是的，你知道，而他们是
they're having a hard time understanding
他们很难理解
you know some of the magic this you know
你知道一些魔术，你知道
this is a lot of great techniques to be
这是很多很棒的技术
able to get boot to tell you what it's
能够启动以告诉您它是什么
doing on one other one Greg that I heard
我听到对方在做格雷格
about from Christa folder was that on
关于Christa文件夹的内容是
the live beans graph in in spring tool
spring tool中的活 bean 图
suite is also another interesting way of
套件也是另一种有趣的方式
figuring out what actually gets created
弄清楚实际上创建了什么
at runtime and and you know looking
在运行时，你知道
around for for being properties is that
周围的属性是
one you've ever tried playing with
您曾经尝试过的一种
they're not really I have not worked at
他们不是我没工作过的地方
that one but it
那一个，但是
sound really interesting they are
听起来真的很有趣
putting a lot of effort over there they
他们在那里付出了很多努力
recently added support spring tool suite
最近添加了支持spring工具套件
if you use a camel for application dot
如果您使用骆驼作为应用程序点
your application out you animal file
您的应用程序出了动物文件
they've added support to basically help
他们增加了支持，基本上可以帮助您
you autocomplete property settings oh
您会自动完成属性设置哦
that's right yeah you know some suppose
是的，是的，你知道一些
I was getting support for that so it's
我得到了支持，所以
all kinds of support and I you know I
各种各样的支持，我知道
take this as an opportunity to say you
借此机会说你
know if you look in and understand all
知道你是否看过并了解所有
these auto-configuration
这些自动配置
things are how they work it can inspire
事情是他们如何发挥作用的
you to go put some Auto configuration
你去放一些自动配置
stuff into your own code yep exactly
完全放入您自己的代码中
for you know maybe even contribute an
因为你知道甚至可以贡献一个
auto configuration back at community oh
自动配置回社区哦
okay um Greg thank you so much this is
好的，格雷格，非常感谢你，这是
been great I learned a lot I'm even
太好了，我学到了很多东西，甚至
watching this for the second time um so
第二次看这个，所以
great if you want to join us for some of
很棒，如果您想加入我们
our upcoming webinars we've got a bunch
我们即将举行的网络研讨会有很多
of cool stuff in the works if you let's
如果您愿意的话，还有很多很棒的作品
see I'm just going to paste a couple of
看到我要粘贴几个
the couple than a couple of these links
这对夫妇比这些链接中的几个
in the top of the chat window so you can
在聊天窗口顶部，以便您可以
get to them I started off the
到他们那里我开始
presentation with a couple links about
介绍与几个链接
what's coming up um and I'm just posting
嗯，我刚发布
them here now so June 23rd June 9th and
他们现在在这里，所以6月23日6月9日，
then again on June 30th so please come
然后在6月30日再来一次，所以请来
back and join us we're going to be
返回并加入我们，我们将成为
having let's see I'm just trying to
让我们看看我只是想
paste the last one in here there we go
将最后一个粘贴到此处，然后开始
on the 9th Adam gonna from turkcell it's
在第九届亚当将从turkcell那里
going to be talking about a
将要谈论一个
comprehensive kind of spring whirlwind
全面的春季旋风
tour
游览
they got tasked to rewrite an
他们受命重写
application in an extremely short time
在极短的时间内应用
frame and did so quite successfully
框架，并取得了相当成功
using food a good chunk of the spring IO
在春季IO中大量使用食物
platform so this is going to be
平台，所以这将是
basically him talking about his
基本上他在谈论他的
experience at Turkcell you know applying
您知道在Turkcell申请的经验
this stuff in anger you know and great
愤怒中的这些东西你知道而且很棒
is a you know just a great case study I
你知道我只是一个很好的案例研究
think it's really really interesting to
认为这真的很有趣
see how customers apply this stuff um on
了解客户如何将这些东西应用到
June 23rd
6月23日
talking a little bit more on Cloud
在云上谈论更多
Foundry so if you're interested in
铸造厂，如果您对此感兴趣
things like Jenkins and continuous
詹金斯（Jenkins）和连续
integration continuous delivery there's
整合持续交付
going to be session on how spring apps
即将举行的春季应用会议
sort of work with continuous integration
持续集成的工作
and Cloud Foundry specifically with with
和Cloud Foundry专门用于
Jenkins from cloudBees and then on June
Jenkins来自cloudBees，然后是六月
30th Phil Dustin's going to join us from
30th Phil Dustin将从以下位置加入我们
icon health and fitness these guys were
图标健康和健身这些家伙
on the webinar program last year
在去年的网络研讨会计划中
absolutely hilarious webinar they talked
他们交谈的绝对有趣的网络研讨会
about how they managed to create a
关于他们如何设法创建一个
shopping cart app in 24 hours using
24小时内使用
spring totally ridiculous certainly not
春天完全荒谬，当然不是
an architecture that even they would
即使他们也会
recommend nor nor pivotal would
推荐也不是关键
recommend but you know the point is they
推荐，但是你知道的是他们
did it like it's just really really
真的是真的吗
funny talk and they're going to be
有趣的谈话，他们将成为
coming and joining us on the 30th
来参加我们三十号
talking about how to just get off J STL
谈论如何下车J STL
and then you know use use timely and
然后您知道及时使用
just Java template add java templating
只是Java模板添加Java模板
their experiences with Java templating
他们使用Java模板的经验
in general um so cool last thing I just
总的来说，嗯，太酷了，我只是
want to mention is of course this is
要说的当然是这个
being recorded so if you want to you
被记录下来，所以如果你想
know take this recording share with
知道与这个录音分享
coworkers bring it to your next
同事将其带到您的下一个
brown-bag lunch or your lunch and learn
午餐或午餐，学习
whatever come um you know sign up for
不管你知道参加什么
the atom feed at spring do /blog and
在spring上原子输入/ blog和
then you'll get a notification when the
那么当您
replay has been posted to youtube you'll
重播已发布到YouTube，您将
also get all the great information that
同时获得所有重要信息
is written up in the blog's spring one
写在博客的春季一
replays and you know all the awesome
重播，您知道所有的超赞
stuff that comes out on the spring blog
春天博客上出现的东西
on including the the webinar replay and
关于网络研讨会重播以及
we'll have that and the slides available
我们将有可用的幻灯片
for you within two weeks often we get to
在两周之内为您服务
it a lot faster than that it just just
它比它快很多
kind of depends frankly so last thing is
坦白地说，所以最后一件事是
just that you know if you want to get
只是您知道您是否想要
your hands on spring booth bits we have
您将手放在春季展位上
not really enabled HTTP downloads
尚未真正启用HTTP下载
directly on purpose it's just horrible
直接是故意的，太可怕了
experience
经验
downloading HTTP directly really
直接下载HTTP
strongly recommend the use maven or
强烈建议使用Maven或
Gradle if you're on a military network
如果您在军事网络上，可以摇篮
or close network or you don't otherwise
或关闭网络，否则您不会
have access to to maven central or you
有权访问Maven Central或您
don't have your own
没有自己的
local on your firewall you know our
在您的防火墙本地，您知道我们
factory server you you can get HDTV
工厂服务器，您可以获得高清电视
downloads if you're absolutely desperate
如果您绝对绝望，请下载
from repo dot spring dot IO um and you
来自repo dot spring dot IO um和您
know it's we don't really make it super
知道这不是我们真正做到的超级
easy but it is a it is possible so
容易，但这是可能的
anyway I put a note there um if you're
无论如何，如果你在
if you're curious for more with that
如果您对此感兴趣的话
correct I just wanna say thanks that was
正确，我只想说谢谢那是
awesome learned a lot and any closing
很棒的东西学到了很多东西
comments before we call it a wrap
评论，然后我们称之为环绕
now that was good I hope to see
现在那很好，我希望看到
everybody at spring one this year me too
大家今年春天我也
yeah Greg's going to kill it at spring
是的，格雷格会在春天杀死它
one we've got a pretty amazing line-up
我们有一个非常了不起的阵容
so check out the website spring 1/2 GX
请查看网站spring 1/2 GX
and register today make sure you do it
并立即注册以确保您这样做
before June 9th so you don't miss the
在6月9日之前，这样您就不会错过
super early bird discount and hopefully
超级早鸟折扣，希望
we will see you in Washington DC
我们将在华盛顿特区见到您
thank you very much everyone and have a
非常感谢大家，有一个
great day bye bye
伟大的一天再见
you
您